Rohit Dhimal

Contact

Toronto +1 437 971 9421 rohit.dhimal19@gmail.com https://rohitdhimal.com.np/ A Computer and Technology enthusiast with experience in web development and design works. I can implement various Front-end and UI/UX and web development elements to make a project look great. My Greatest Strength is I am a team player and curious person who seeks to learn more driven by innovation, creativity, and finding solutions.

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/rohit-dhimal-271a80155/

Dribbble

https://dribbble.com/rohitdhimal19

500px

https://500px.com/p/rohitdhimal19

Key Skills

Photoshop, Illustrator, Figma, Adobe, Wireframe, Graphics Designing, UI/UX Designing, HTML5, CSS, ES6, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Foundation, React, Node.js, Tailwind CSS, JSON, API, UI, UX, OOP, SQL, Agile, Python, WordPress, PHP, Heroku, GitHub, jQuery, git, MySQL, TypeScript, Teamwork

Experience

July 2020 – March 2021

Frontend Web Developer and Graphics Designer • Namuma Computers Pvt. Ltd.

- . Developed and maintained a website using HTML, CSS3, JS, React, and Laravel (back end).
- . Create Responsive design.
- . Deploy website in live server and help user to use WordPress.
- . Create Wireframe and User Centric Design.
- . Collaborated in designing REST API in Laravel.
- . Create custom designs and illustrations using Photoshop and illustrator.
- . Code Reviewing and Unit testing the codes.
- . Create UI/UX for web projects.

Oct 2020 - Dec 2020

IT Officer and Graphics Designer • NepalBahas.com

- . Create Custom flyers, illustrations, and banners thumbnails for social media
- . Help and manage the content creators' computers.

Education

2021-2023

Lambton College

Computer Software and Database Development

2017-2020

University of Wolverhampton

B.S.C (Hons) in Computer Science